♪ In the not too
distant future ♪
♪ Somewhere in time and space ♪
♪ Mike Nelson and
his robot pals ♪
♪ Are caught in
an endless chase ♪
♪ Pursued by a woman
whose name is Pearl ♪
♪ An evil gal who wants
to rule the world ♪
♪ She threw a few
things in her purse ♪
♪ And in her rocket
ship she hunts him ♪
♪ All across the universe ♪
- [Pearl] I'll get you!
♪ I'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst I can
find, la la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And I'll monitor
his mind, la la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end, la la la ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of
his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot Roll Call ♪
- Cambot!
- You're on!
- Gypsy!
- Oh my stars!
- Tom Servo!
- Check me out!
- Crow!
- I'm different!
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science
facts, la la la ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself,
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(doors slamming)
- Hey everyone, welcome
to the Satellite of Love.
You know, since we are stuck
in orbit over ancient Rome,
I thought it might be a
good time to teach the bots
a little something
about history.
- Mike, this
encyclopedia is worthless
for my biography of Roland Gift.
- Yeah, Mike, it's really old.
It lists Hitler as a
fairly stable veteran
of the Great War.
- Oh come on,
they're not that
old, they're fine.
- Oh yeah?
It mentions the light
bulb as a charming theory.
- Yeah, and congress
is spelled with an F.
What is a gongreff?
- Well I used 'em when I was
a kid, they seemed fine then.
- The periodic table has
three elements in it, Mike!
- There's a volume for
the letter epsilon.
- There's a mailing
address for Machu Picchu.
- It's got a picture
of Stonehenge.
- So?
- Under construction.
- Yeah.
- Oh, well, so what you
high-minded encyclopedia snobs
are trying to tell me
is you want a new set.
Fine, I'll get you a new set.
- Anything that's not
hand written on papyrus
will do.
- Yeah.
- That's very funny,
we'll be right back.
You know, they got
me through college.
- You never finished
college, Mike.
- Oh yeah.
(Crow sighing)
(upbeat music)
- I mean, look, some day
we hope to harness fire
to serve man, not
simply terrorize him
with horrifying randomness.
- Yeah, yeah, and
here's a whole section
on our deadly foes,
the dinosaurs.
(Mike groaning)
- Okay, you bellyachers,
got you a brand-spanking-new
set of encyclopedias,
each page with an
internet up link
so you can constantly
update 'em.
- Man, this is
incredibly up to date.
- Wow, 27 pages on
Gwen Stefani alone.
- Amazing.
- Well, I think I've more
than answered your
encyclopedia grievances.
- No.
- No!
It was much more fun to
complain about the old ones
than to have new ones.
- Yeah, yeah, I miss
complaining already, frankly.
- I gotta check in on
that planet down there,
down there you know?
(vocalizing)
- Thank you, Maximus.
Oh, hi Mike.
Well, this whole Roman thing
has taken a turn for the crappy.
Flavia here discovered
we weren't gods and all
and had us thrown into
this slimy dungeon.
And they're being pretty
rough on pale face here,
they took away his brain
which sucks for him.
- I like fruit, fruit is good.
- [Flavia] Talk, hirsute one.
Do you plot against
our beloved Emperor?
- [Bobo] Oh, please, I
can't stand it anymore!
(crying)
- And Bobo, man,
they are totally
torturing him right now.
I mean, it's bad, Mike.
You guys should probably
write to Amnesty International
House of Pancakes or whatever.
Oh, I broke a nail.
(Bobo hooting)
(Woman laughing)
- Talk, smelly fake god.
- I'll say anything
you want, just give me
some of that yummy mutton!
- Is it safe?
- I don't care if it's
safe, it smells delicious!
Give me!
- Treasonous fool!
- The Emperor's about to
give his violin recital
upstairs, ma'am.
- Ooh, right.
Listen, I must go
but I'll be back
and you three will
be like so tortured,
it's like not even funny.
(laughing)
- No, no!
- So, Mike, here's the deal.
If you help us out of this one,
I promise I'll let you and
your little wind up toys go
and you'll never have to watch
another lousy movie again.
- Yes, yes, do it, Mike!
- No more crummy movies?
- Do it, come on!
- Do it, do it!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey!
- Yes, yes, yes, yes!
- [Both] Hey, hey, hey!
- I don't know, Pearl, I mean
you've lied to us before.
- I know!
But it wasn't my fault,
in a way that I haven't
quite figured out yet.
But this time for real.
I mean, how are you gonna
get out of this stupid,
stinky Roman time
without us anyway?
- She's right, Mike.
I don't wanna have
to see you in toga.
(shuddering)
- I don't know.
Okay, what do you want me to do?
- I need you to come down
here and get brain guy's
brain for us, they put
it too far out of range
so he's at quarter
power, which means
he's even more of
an idiot than usual.
- Pearl, tell me about
the rabbits again, please?
- And pathetic as it
is, he's our only hope,
so I'm gonna have him bring
you down here to fetch it.
Okay, brain guy, send Mike down.
- Send Mike down.
Okay.
- Oh, dude!
(sneezing)
I'm allergic.
- Not goose down, you dope!
Bring Mike down!
- Mike, everyone says
you're ugly and dumb
and no one likes you.
(chuckling)
(Mike chuckling)
- Oh come on,
they do not, really?
Oh man, really?
Oh man, that really
brought me down.
- Mike.
(chuckling)
- Listen, you
empty-headed albino,
I said bring Mike down here!
- Okay, nice lady.
- Oh, my, what am I doing here?
I was just at a 401K
planning meeting.
Oh, by the way, my name's
Mike Down, I'm a CPA.
(clanging)
(Observer groaning)
- Thank you.
- This might take
a minute, Mike.
In the meantime,
why don't you enjoy
your final bad movie
ever, I promise.
It's a real piece of
cheese called Space Mutiny.
Hey, brain low, think you
can manage sending a movie?
- Okay.
- Should I set up my
overhead projector now?
- You pipe down.
(alarm blaring)
- Movie!
- Maybe Carter likes
me or something.
Ooh, Gypsy likes me, that's it!
(doors clanging)
(suspenseful music)
- [Tom] Amazingly
Idiotic Productions.
(chuckling)
- [Mike] That's good.
- [Crow] A Jonathan Winters,
Billie Holiday production.
(awe-inspiring music)
(gasping)
- David Winters.
- Oh, we're in good hands.
- [Tom] 20 exclusive hits
by the original artists!
- [Mike] Sounds like
someone owns himself
a DX7 keyboard, huh?
- [Crow] Whoa, whoa,
watch out, watch out!
- [Tom] I have my doubts that
this movie is starring anyone.
- [Mike] It's just
the usual stable
of David Winters' actors.
- [Tom] Yay, oh, no, wait.
Oh, because she's
Cameron Mitchell's, wait.
- [Crow] His nickname is Tiny.
- [Tom] Featuring
music normally heard
at the Days Inn lounge
in Columbia Heights.
(awe-inspiring music)
- [Mike] Passed from
editor to editor
in a desperate
attempt to save it.
- [Crow] There's gonna
be seven levels of Hell
in this movie too.
- [Tom] Deb, big favor,
can you associate produce?
Thanks.
- [Crow] Hope John
and Holiday DeKock?
- [Mike] What
kinda name is that?
And completely botched
by David Winters.
- [Tom] Outlets in space.
- 13 generations ago--
- Wow.
- [Narrator] Our overpopulated
world built the Southern Sun.
- [Mike] No we didn't.
- [Narrator] A
self-sufficient spaceship
that would be home to
thousands of migrants.
With a 10-light-year
journey to a new
and un-colonized world.
- Cool, huh?
- [Narrator] Our current
descendants have come to accept
the Southern Sun as their home
and work for a better
future for their children.
- [Mike] They're known as dupes.
- [Narrator] While
most of the inhabitants
of this generation are content,
there are some who have
grown restless and impatient.
- [Tom] Like Pat Riley
here, for instance.
(suspenseful music)
- [Crow] Where the hell did I
put that old ping pong table?
- [Mike] I have this
feeling I'm being followed
by a lobster boy.
(Tom chuckling)
- [Crow] Still, he's
not nearly as creepy
as most meter readers.
- [Tom] He's like an
Armand Assante wannabe.
- [Mike] Show you how to
use a label maker properly.
- [Crow] He made a bomb out
of soap and Paco Rabanne.
- [Announcer] Attention, prepare
for shuttle lancer landing.
- [Mike] Melissa Manchester!
- [Pilot] Lancer
to Southern Sun,
located rescue
beacon and survivors,
they're all female and identify
themselves as Bellerians.
We have initiated
landing procedures
and are returning to base.
- [Tom] I could watch
this stuff all day, Mike.
- [Mike] Oh, you will.
- [Lemont] You will
enter the Southern Sun
in figures five millennium
and your docking bay
is one niner, over.
- [Pilot] Roger,
shuttle lancer locked
to guidance control, over.
(vocalizing)
♪ Lame ♪
- [Mike] Shuttle craft
determined to be cute, sir.
(beeping)
- [Pilot] Shuttle
landing successful.
Bellerian survivors
disembarking.
- Attention, all hands.
- Dungeon.
- [Announcer] Shuttle
landing complete.
Prepare for incoming
Stingray Viper Squadron.
- [Pilot] Red two,
Southern Sun in sight.
- [Tom] S'cuse me.
S'cuse me.
- Attention.
- S'cuse me.
- All those wishing to meet
the incoming Viper
Squadron proceed
to the docking bay.
- Who's that?
- Lea!
- Hi, Dad!
Hi Scott.
- Hi!
- Ah, so pretty.
- If you're going down
to the docking bay
to meet your friend from
Coreolus you better hurry.
- Oi!
- The Viper's in final approach.
- Well I came down to check
that he's on the flight.
- Lieutenant Lemont!
- Mac.
(Tom growling)
- Contact the pilot
of the Stingray Viper
and ask if Professor
Spooner is aboard.
- I'm insane!
- Thank you.
- Sun Control, I have a request.
Do you have a Professor
Spooner on board?
Over.
- Stingray to Sun Control,
affirmative, over.
- [Crow] Sting, Debbie
Reynolds and God.
- Bye, Dad.
- Bye bye.
- Bye, Scott.
- Bye.
- [Pilot] Southern Sun,
we are starting our
landing sequence.
- [Mike] In the future,
geese will be rocket powered.
- [Stingray Two] Southern
Sun, abort landing,
we have pirates coming
up fast on our tail!
Stingray Two to Stingray
Three, we are under fire,
prepare for defense formation.
- [Stingray Three]
Roger, Stingray Two.
- [Tom] Graphics by Kenner.
- [Stingray One] Stingray One,
assuming defense formation,
we'll cover for you
and the professor.
(alarms blaring)
- What the hell's
going on out there?
- [Pilot] Look out, Red Three!
Red Three is down.
- [Crow] I never liked
Red Three anyway.
- Damn it!
(vocalizing)
♪ Crap ♪
- [Pilot] Pirate
ship eliminated.
- [Mike] Special effects by
Industrial Light and Morons.
(lasers firing)
- [Pilot] Good shot, Ryder.
- [Tom] Are we the good
guys or the bad guys?
- [Announcer]
Attention, all hands,
man your battle stations,
we're under attack.
- [Mike] Uh-oh, an air
show, look out below!
- [Crow] I told you we
should've landed at LaGuardia.
Tell me about it, these
briefs I'm wearin' huh?
(Tom chuckling)
- [Mike] So their spaceship
has a huge basement.
(Tom humming)
- [Tom] Say...
- [Man] Commander
Kalgan, can I help you?
- [Crow] Calgon?
- Excuse me, Sir.
- Did you have a reservation?
- [Man] Commander, Sir,
what are you doing?
(beeping)
- [Mike] The hostess will
seat you in a moment, sir!
We have a perfectly fine bar
if you'd like to wait there.
Oh, I see.
Oh great, yeah, shooting
me is not gonna get you to
a table any faster, sir.
(man groaning)
I'll get the manager.
- [Tom] Kalgan, blow me away.
(upbeat music)
- [Mike] Does that guy inflate
his pants to attract mates?
(exploding)
- [Tom] Good work, you
blew up the septic tank.
- [Crow] Oh no, I just tried
to open my garage door,
what the?
(beeping)
- [Computer] Warning,
system power loss.
- [Tom] Too right!
- Energize our
emergency landing strip.
- We're off circuit!
It's dead, sir.
- Guidance system failing!
(Tom laughing)
- We lost power!
- [Mike] Relax, you're
in your own room.
- We lost power!
(static hissing)
- [Tom] Is it a good idea for
a pilot to eject in space?
- [Computer] Viper out of
control, collision imminent.
Pilot emergency beam down
ejection system activated.
- Attention all hands,
(Tom hissing)
prepare for crash landing.
(ship exploding)
- [Crow] So really,
how does this help
the Basque separatists?
(man yelling)
- Scott!
- My stair stepper!
- [Announcer] Attention,
pilot beam down successful.
Medical team, stand by,
fire control to docking bay.
(explosion booming)
(Tom chuckling)
- Look out, it's gonna blow!
(Mike laughing)
It's gonna blow!
- [Tom] If the first 10
minutes are any indication,
this movie's gonna blow!
(crew yelling)
- [Crow] My Buns of Steel
videos are in there!
- We have to get him!
- We don't have time!
- It's gonna blow!
- He'll burn alive!
- Come on, Mother.
(ship exploding)
- [Tom] Oh, yeah,
that'll take care of it.
- [Lea] My god, the Professor.
(Kalgan chuckling)
- [Mike] Remember
Carl's blonde joke?
(Kalgan laughing)
- What happened, Lieutenant?
- The Viper was locked into
the Sun's guidance control,
Commander, and we lost power!
- Commander, the energizing
turbines have been sabotaged.
- Sabotaged?
- [Tom] But what of the little
children and their toys?
- [Crow] John Waters.
- Headquarters.
- Blake here.
Give me Kalgan.
- He's right here, go ahead.
- Sir, I just saw something I
thought you should know about.
Some strange women came
on board with the Lancer.
- Strange women.
- I'm sorry the information
is so scanty, but I'll
send you up more--
- Scanty?
- As I get it.
Blake out.
- [Mike] Hey, look at
this, the office newsletter
says I look like Susan Powter.
- [Tom] Santa's playing
FreeCell over here.
(computer beeping)
- Oh man, what'd I do?
- What do you think, Devers?
- [Crow] Should I spend
20 bucks for Griffey?
- I think whoever did this knows
his way around space ships.
- I agree.
- I don't know if this helps
but ho ho ho.
- On thing's for sure,
we've gotta reduce
speed drastically
'til we repair the damage.
You know, I'm thinking more
about the possible motive.
Why?
(Tom laughing)
- Commander?
- Ho?
- Ho.
- You get a computer readout
on the damage in
the docking bay.
Also, the pirate
fleet's position
and load the file
into the computer.
I'd like to do some research
on our new female guests,
the Bellerians.
- Nude research!
- I want that ready
as soon as possible.
- Aye aye, Sir.
- Thank you, Devers.
(mysterious music)
- [Tom] So, we've got
some Benedictine monks
in the floorboards,
unfortunately.
We have set some traps with
fresh bread and brandy, though.
- Ladies?
This is your new home.
I know it doesn't
look like much,
but if you'll bear with us,
I'm sure we can make
you quite comfortable.
- [Jennera] Leave, we
Bellerians wish to be alone.
This place will
serve our purpose.
Leave.
- [Tom] Whoa, drank
too much Surge.
- [Crow] Bryce, you okay?
- It's a pleasure
having you on board.
- [Tom] I guess.
- Gentlemen.
- [Tom] Oh, and by
the way, ladies,
there's a ferret cage by
the wall if you need it.
(suspenseful music)
- [Crow] Well, I polished
the back corridor,
anyone else need
their room done?
- [Mike] Hey, you
guys, I got my dad's
Enforcer for the weekend.
(Kalgan chuckling)
- [Tom] We have fun, huh?
- [Crow] Can you help
me out of this thing?
- [Kalgan] Our
timing was perfect.
Two for the price of one.
- We had a coupon.
- Who would've thought
that one small spacecraft--
- [Crow] Robbie Robertson.
- Could've done
that much damage?
- That Viper's missile
pod took out the entire
winching system to
the docking bay doors.
- [Tom] Man, you
should've been there!
- According to
the damage reports
from the Chief
Maintenance Engineer,
it'll take at least two
weeks before the docking bay
can be used again.
- I know, it's great.
- Couldn't have
wished for it better.
(Tom chuckling)
- That means the Southern
Sun is completely isolated.
(Tom snickering)
Nobody can enter her.
And more important,
nobody can leave her.
(Tom laughing)
- Excellent.
They no longer have a choice.
(laughing)
- [Mike] God, you look good.
- It was cruel fate
to be born in space.
But I have vowed we
will not die here.
It is my destiny to set
my feet upon a real world
and to accumulate
wealth and power
beyond our wildest dreams.
(chuckling)
I have offered the people
of the Southern Sun a rich,
new life.
- That's good.
- And now they
have no alternative
but to accept my
generosity and alter course
for Corona Borealis.
- Ooh.
(laughing)
- Don't you love it?
You know, we're always laughing,
you and me, it's great.
- Lieutenant.
- Oi.
- What's the report
from damage control?
- It's not complete
yet, Captain.
But the first reports
indicate that two of our
(Tom hissing)
LM5000 accion drive motors
have been sabotaged.
- Boy.
- This also affects
the performance
of one of our vixon
piles drive generators.
- Oi.
- Give me a computer readout
on our whole stress factor.
- Sir.
- [Devers] Reduce
speed by two thirds.
Shut down two of
our booster engines.
- Yes, sir.
- Oh, one other thing.
- [Crow] Oi!
- Can you establish video
contact with the docking bay?
- One of the missiles
from the Viper took out
the video control
tower down there.
But we are trying to
reestablish contact
with a sarid video robot.
- [Tom] Did you sign
Sherry's birthday card?
(dramatic music)
- We've been in space too long!
Let us land the ship.
We can do it, we have the power!
- It's true, we have
the power to do this!
- Yes.
- But this would directly
oppose the law of the universe!
- Yes.
- The law of the galaxy!
- Forget the law!
- No!
No, the law must be
upheld, we cannot break it.
- Oh, okay so we--
- Gentlemen.
It seems that we are
not all in agreement.
- [Tom] I disagree!
- Engineer Parsons
seems content to spend
his remaining years
upon the Southern Sun.
- Then let him do so, alone.
- [Man] Yeah, that's right!
- This is mutiny,
this is treason,
which I warn you, I must report.
- [Crow] I just have
to wet myself first.
- Will you allow him
to spoil your ambitions
for a greater future?
- [Man] Not allow that!
- [Tom] The easily
led wise council.
- [Mike] What I meant
was I totally endorse
what you're doing, ow!
- [Crow] Rip his band uniform,
then he'll have to pay for it!
- [Tom] Next they're
gonna give him books
so they can dump 'em.
- Okay.
- Right over here.
- [Crow] Death by snicker-snag.
- [Man] Hold him, hold him.
- [Mike] I'm gonna
inflate him to 35 pounds.
- [Tom] Okay, then, moving on
to number three on our agenda,
Sherry's birthday party.
- Are there any other of you
that wish to confuse
freedom with treason?
- [Mike] I'd like to confuse
bok choy with cabbage, sir.
- Report to the
Enforcer's bridge.
- Let's go, hurry up!
- [Crow] Well it
is the rare meeting
where something
actually got done.
- [Mike] You're strict, sir.
- You have done well.
(doors clanging)
- Alone at last.
(humming)
(gentle instrumental music)
(sighing)
(crashing)
The hell?
- [Crow] Red Norvo, Red Norvo,
this is Goldilocks Niner,
I'm coming in sucker,
prepare to die.
- [Tom] Oh yeah,
well come get some!
(explosion booming)
- Crow, Servo,
what the hell in
Michigan is going on?
- [Crow] I can't talk now, Mike,
I'm locked in a death
struggle with Servo.
- [Tom] Yeah, me too,
Mike, only with Crow, over.
- Cambot, give me rocket
number nine, will ya?
- [Crow] Eat death, Servo!
- [Tom] Eat munchy crunchy
chocolatey cocoa death, Crow!
- [Crow] Enjoy a nice serving
of ground Betty with death,
but mostly eat death.
(explosion booming)
- Crow, Servo?
You guys be careful out there.
- [Crow] Oh, we won't.
(groaning)
Servo, you just ripped
a hole in my torso.
Wee!
(Tom groaning)
- [Tom] Too late for me, I
took a laser blast to the dome.
Wahoo!
- Fellas?
- [Tom] Well, shall we
auger these babies in?
- [Crow] After you.
- I love you, Crow!
- I'm sorta fond of you Servo!
(explosion booming)
- Crow, Servo, you guys okay?
Fellas?
(fire crackling)
Okay, now this
isn't funny anymore.
(Tom laughing)
- Lighten up, Nelson,
we're robots, remember?
- Man, that was great.
- Yeah!
- So where'd you
get the space ships?
- Oh, you mean the hyper
warp escape shuttles
which we just trashed?
- Yeah, those.
- Oh, they've been down
in the hold waiting for
us to use 'em to escape
and stuff like that.
- Oh, I see.
- Yeah.
- So don't you think
we maybe should've used
them for escape purposes?
- What purposes?
- What's he on about?
- Oh, you mean escape from here.
- Oh!
- Oh geez.
How stupid of us, Mike, man.
- Boy, is my face red.
Sorry Mike.
- Oh boy.
- We had escape pods,
we didn't use 'em.
- Wait, isn't there
just one more?
- Oh yeah, Gypsy's got it out,
she'll be along any second now.
- [Gypsy] For England
and the Queen!
- All right, go for it, Gyps!
Take it in.
- We'll be right back.
(upbeat music)
- Oh that was fun!
- That was great, man.
- Scott Devers.
- Dave Ryder.
- Pleased to me
you, shall we do it?
- [Tom] Oh, this is sudden.
- Lieutenant.
- Sir?
- Please file this.
- Certainly, sir.
- Thank you.
- [Mike] You know where I
could get some Zubaz, man?
- Commander Jansen.
- Well, welcome aboard,
Mr. Ryder, you've met
our Captain, Devers?
Sit down, son.
- Thank you, sir.
- All right and could I have
your space status card, please?
Thank you.
- Sorry it's so moist.
(beeping)
- [Tom] You've got mail.
- Well there we have it,
any questions, Mr. Ryder?
- Sir, I'd like to see a
video of the crash, if I may.
- Good idea, come this way.
- [Tom] I'll show
you where my elves
are working day and night.
- Take a chair.
- [Crow] And ram it.
(murmuring)
- Lieutenant.
- Yes, sir?
- Could you punch up a
video of the crash, please?
- Yes sir.
- On our computer.
- [Computer] Disaster analysis.
Guidance system engaged.
You are now on the--
- Oi?
- Southern Sun's guidance--
- Ho.
- Control system, over.
Pilot control released.
Warning, critical power loss.
- [Tom] We now switch
live to Spencer's Gifts.
- [Mike] Hey Macarena.
- [Tom] Ayyyy.
(Mike laughing)
- [Crow] It's a Wicca
Tupperware party.
(mysterious music)
- [Mike] Steve called?
- [Crow] My poultice.
- [Mike] Oh, I've got this
itch right on my leg there.
- [Crow] Look familiar, Mike?
Oh, what am I saying, no way.
- [Mike] Hey.
- [Tom] Damn Swedish
ergonomic chairs,
how do you sit
comfortably on these?
- [Crow] Get a bunch
of women together,
it's either witchery
or a wedding shower.
That's what I say.
- [Tom] Mother
Angelica aerobics.
- [Mike] I heard that.
- [Crow] I better get
the phone, you guys.
- [Jennera] You
received our message.
I'm glad you've come,
we've been waiting for you.
- [Man] Hey you, the
Bellerians are off limits.
- [Tom] You've never heard
of the getting some clause?
- [Commander] Well,
there we are, gentlemen.
Tell me, Dave--
- Slab bulkhead.
- Your Viper was
equipped with a new
high-density deatomizer
escape system, right?
- Yes, Commander.
Right now it only works
over very short distances.
But who knows what the future
potential of it could be.
- What about the professor?
- What's his max?
- Commander, I'm sorry
about the professor.
There's nothing I could've done.
The system's only hooked
up to the Viper pilot.
- Don't blame yourself, son.
- [Crow] It's not your
fault you're a chunk head.
- You're lucky you're alive.
You're lucky you saved yourself.
- [Tom] I can't breathe.
(groaning)
- Lea.
You had us all worried.
Please, next time
there's a fire,
leave it to damage control.
You okay?
- Okay?
Next time, young lady,
you stay out of the way.
- Dad, I was there, the
pilot chickened out,
otherwise Spooner would
be alive right now!
- David Ryder, I want you
to meet my daughter, Lea.
- [Mike] We're
about the same age.
- Professor never had a chance.
There's nothing I could've
done to prevent it.
- Oh, so you left him to die--
- Lea!
Stop it.
- He ejected and he's alive!
- Listen, lady!
- Doctor!
- Doctor Lady!
- I don't have to justify
my actions to you!
But since you're asking,
that explosion cut the power
and there wasn't time to
go over to the auxiliary
back up system!
I had to eject, I
had no other choice!
- [Tom] That's Doctor
I Had No Other Choice!
- Commander, Captain,
excuse me, I have
to file my report.
- [Mike] Coach will
totally ream me
if I don't file my report.
- [Commander] Lea.
- [Tom] You're getting
a lump of coal.
- [Crow] I like
playing with the knobs.
- [Mike] All you
can eat me tonight.
- [Woman] Excuse me, sir,
I think you'll find
this interesting.
- Yes, what is it?
- [Woman] It's an inventory
of all the explosives
under our control.
- [Tom] Hey, one
of the New Monkees.
- [Crow] Oh, Gopher,
are you lost?
- [Mike] He's calling
to check on his gender.
- Give me an audio video link
of bridge to console seven.
Please hurry.
- There's something coming
through on the voice monitor
from the engine room area.
- Wow.
- Put it through on five.
- [Tom] The
electrolysis is working.
- [Crow] Those Formica monitors
don't have a lot of resolution.
- My name is Flight
Lieutenant Lemont.
(Tom hissing)
- Well according to my printout
from the supply
store's inventory,
we're definitely
short on conventional
ballistic explosive.
I mean, I've double checked.
Somebody with direct
online access to Central
has been transferring
large amounts
of explosives--
- Lobster.
- And then simply
covering the requisition.
I wouldn't have
found out about it
unless Central asked me
to confirm acceptance
of 100 units of chemo
plastic and atomic compound.
I mean, that's crazy, can
you imagine that amount
of explosives lying around
the ship's engine room?
- [Tom] Come on, skull,
pop out of my skin.
- [Steve] I think
I've traced who it is.
- Who in the hell
is he talking to?
Put it through to the bridge.
- [Steve] I want to speak to
somebody from Command, please.
- [Mike] Excuse me, Al Lewis.
- Okay, for the
sake of security,
I think it would be
better if you came up here
and asked for me,
Lieutenant Lemont.
- Send a couple of
men over there to stop
that engineer before
he gets to the bridge.
Unless I get to him first.
- Time me!
Go ahead.
- [Tom] Well I think I
just had to report this,
I mean, I really
thought about it
and I think I really
have to report this.
I really, really
have to report it.
- [Mike] Herbie, the misfit elf.
(suspenseful music)
- [Crow] He looks
like Billie Jean King.
- [Mike] Oh no, snowmobilers!
- [Tom] I've seen this
before, compulsory splatball.
- [Crow] You know, if we
pretend we know what's going on,
this is actually
kind of exciting.
- [Mike] Oh, he's
above the stage,
now he's gonna fall right
in at the end of the opera.
- [Tom] Doesn't this
basement make the space ship
kinda bottom heavy?
(Kalgan chuckling)
- [Crow] See, I
can throw my laugh.
(Kalgan chuckling)
(Tom laughing)
- [Crow] Come on,
give me your bio notes
or I'll get a D, come on, man.
- Third engineer, Steve Codell?
- [Tom] Known as
Stinky to his friends.
- You have two choices.
- Soup or muffin.
- Join me or the deep freeze.
- I prefer to jump, Kalgan.
- [Crow] And by the way,
Calgon, we need more of you.
- Be my guest.
- [Mike] Oh, the death
of Rick Springfield.
(Steve yelling)
- [Tom] I just wish
I had Jessie's girl!
- [Mike] Ooh, he had a
mouthful of Starburst.
(Kalgan laughing)
- [Crow] Oh, and then
they TP'd him, nice.
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] They have the best
minigolf in the galaxy.
- [Mike] What are those, is
she raising recycling bins?
- [Dave] Hi!
- [Crow] Could I get a spot?
- Got a nice place here.
- Yeah, bite my nice place.
- Listen,
I understand how you feel.
- [Mike] It's Doctor Listen,
I Understand How You Feel.
- You?
How could you know how I feel?
- Listen, lady, I
did what I had to do.
Don't you think I
realize a good man died?
A man I respected and love?
Hey, I don't need this!
- Wait.
- [Tom] They miss a
couple of lines here?
- I wasn't aware
that you knew him.
- What difference does it make?
He's dead and there's
nothing we can do about it.
- [Crow] Now married to
an entertainment lawyer
in Sherman Oaks.
- Forget it, I don't need this!
- [Mike] This is like when I
plateaued on my delts, man.
- [Tom] She's a
sexy senior citizen.
- [Crow] Shake
it, Ralph Macchio!
(energetic music)
- [Tom] Hey, Mike, I
bet you were really into
the Thompson Twins, right, huh?
You were Wang Chunging all
over the place, huh, huh?
- [Mike] You know, I hate
it when the chaperones
start dancing with the kids.
- [Crow] So in the future
there's absolutely no shame.
- [Tom] Oh, my pantyhose are
itchy, pantyhose are itchy.
Itchy, itchy, itchy.
Oh, oh, itchy.
(energetic music)
(Tom laughing)
- [Mike] Man, Shari
Lewis has got it goin on!
- [Crow] Oh mama!
Or grandmama, I guess.
- [Tom] Oh, you know,
without Metrecal,
this would not be possible.
- [Mike] Man, I'd rather get
a table dance from Trent Lott.
- What is she thinking, I'm
a weight lifter, come on.
- [Mike] This is less subtle
than an Annie Sprinkle
performance piece.
- [Tom] Oh, she's
presenting like a mandrill!
(groaning)
- [Crow] Two for one
techno drinks, cool.
(Tom laughing)
- [Mike] Did you see my butt?
- [Tom] I don't need this.
- Is a woman allowed to buy
a man a drink in your galaxy?
- [Crow] I guess it's okay.
- Kind of depends upon
the man now doesn't it?
- On what?
- I dunno.
- Whether or not he
wants to accept it.
- [Tom] Wow, it's like
Nick and Nora Charles.
- I see.
You're still angry.
- Checking...
- Yeah.
But I'll get over it.
- You know, the professor
taught me everything I know.
- [Mike] It took him 20 seconds.
- Can we start again?
- Yeah, why not?
We made a mess of
it the first time.
Dave Ryder.
- Lea Jansen.
Glad to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- You like it here?
- It's not bad.
(Tom chuckling)
- [Crow] Bennigan's, 1985.
- [Tom] I should show
my butt to that guy.
- That's odd.
- What's that?
- I know that woman over
there, she works on the bridge.
- [Mike] She's got
an awesome package,
I never noticed that before.
- [Lea] She's being ushered out.
- [Dave] Is there
any reason for it?
- [Lea] I don't know.
Looks like she's been arrested.
- [Mike] She's walking
with two Mexican wrestlers.
- Let's go check it out.
- [Tom] It's gotta
be better than this.
- [Mike] Their dancing
has gotten even whiter.
- [Crow] She's got an
armadillo down her trousers.
(Mike laughing)
- Flight Lieutenant Lemont?
- Yes.
- Did you sign Sherry's card?
- Thank you gentlemen.
- You were speaking with
Third Engineer Steve Codell.
- That is my business.
(Crow hissing)
- But now I'm making it mine.
(laser firing)
- [Mike] I dunno, I've
always like the vanilla
sport shakes better,
it's just me.
- [Tom] Tell my wife I love her.
- [Crow] Oh yeah,
sometimes I pass out
when I do a military
after a bench.
- There they go.
- [Mike] Hervé
Villechaize's death car!
- Let's take this.
- Fridge Largemeats.
- Punt Speedchunk.
- [Crow] Butch Deadlift.
- [Mike] You could
walk on your hands
and catch up to the guy.
- [Crow] Put your helmet on,
we'll be reaching
speeds of three.
(Kalgan laughing)
- Hit the siren!
(vocalizing)
- Go!
- [Mike] Let's see
what this lark can do.
- [Crow] We need both
horsepowers on this thing.
- Dave look out!
- Did they just hit a poodle?
- Bastard!
(lasers firing)
- [Mike] We can't go any
faster, I'd have to drop
the waxing compound.
(Tom laughing)
- [Crow] Put the top
up, put the top up!
(Tom vocalizing)
♪ All I wanna say to you ♪
- Hey!
Hey, she's dead!
- Wait a minute!
- She died!
- Wow!
- Sir?
- [Crow] I think
it's very nice of you
to give that dead
woman another chance.
- Your report, sir.
- Thank you, Devers.
- [Tom] A D in comportment?
- You really believe, sir,
that this act of sabotage
has got something to do with
our navigational course?
- Yeah, I'm convinced
and this proves it.
- Ouch.
- I think they wanna drive us
into the neighboring
constellation.
- Helveca?
- Oh, I love that font.
- The constellation of
the Corona Borealis.
Pirate territory.
- Precisely.
- Sir, we have to find
out who's behind this.
Any ideas, Commander?
- Yes.
You know, Captain.
- I have a whole colony
of people living in my beard.
- It's always very
dangerous to speculate.
- [Devers] Yes, sir.
- So it would have to be
somebody on this ship.
- Brilliant!
- To be gained by this.
- Stand to gain.
- That leaves us with what?
- Exactly squat, sir.
- The Flight Master?
The Enforcer?
- Waitress!
She never sees me.
- It's very perilous
for everyone on board.
We do not make wild accusations.
So we keep this top
classified secret.
- [Tom] Top super duper
maxi extreme ultra secret.
- Commander.
- Yes?
- Someone to see you.
- Check it.
- [Mike] Okay, look alive
everybody, oh, sorry Susan,
that's right.
- She's dead.
- [Tom] Get off the Stairmaster!
- [Crow] Bold Bigflank.
- [Mike] Splint Chesthair.
- [Tom] It's Kevorkian!
- Yes?
Can I help you?
- Yes you can,
we're looking for the
Enforcer's headquarters.
- [Crow] We are?
- It really is
awfully lonely here.
Can I show you around?
- [Mike] I was just about
to do the Monster Mash.
- [Tom] Let's see,
what'd I forget to hide
before they came in here?
Oh yeah.
- Come on, let's get
the hell outta here.
- Wait, this looks interesting.
- [Mike] Here at the
underpants testing ground.
- [Crow] Wow these guys died,
lost all their muscle mass, man.
- [Tom] What?
- Would you care for a spot tea?
- [Mike] Because doing
so would be very ironic.
- Well,
we're in a bit of a hurry.
- So we'll take it to go.
- What are all these bodies for?
- A personal collection.
- Collection?
- Yes, when anyone
is under suspicion,
they're immediately
arrested, tortured
and given the truth drug.
(murmuring)
When Kalgan is convinced
they're of no longer use,
he simply has them ejected
into space.
(Crow vocalizing)
However, if they
seem redeemable,
Kalgan freezes them.
- Oh, do they keep well?
- That means all the
Enforcers are corrupt
and Kalgan's running his
own personal army here.
- That's correct.
- How many Enforcers
has Kalgan killed?
- To date, 38.
- So Kalgan's control of
the Enforcers is complete
and any of the Enforcers
that resisted him are dead?
- Or frozen.
- How many enforcers are there?
- [Old Man] Just over 200.
- [Tom] Oh, here comes
Lord of the Dance.
(vocalizing)
- To the deep freeze!
- [Mike] Oh, we're going to
the deep freeze, I must say.
- Well thank you for
calling, do call again.
- [Crow] I'm late for
Roddy McDowall practice.
- With the population and
the crew of the Southern Sun
being so large, surely
we can do something.
- It'd be a bloodbath.
- Well if they've
broken intergalactic
law, that's mutiny,
we can call for help.
- Cannot we?
- It's my guess that Kalgan has
already installed scramblers
in the communications computer.
(upbeat music)
(Crow clearing throat)
- Oh, hey Mike.
I'm a Bellerian.
- Sure looks that
way, doesn't it?
- Yep.
I just found out and
you know, it's weird.
It explains so much
about me, about who I am,
where I came from, what
motivates me and such.
- Well, sure, I mean
you're a Bellerian.
- Yep.
Why, don't I look like one?
- No, sure, you do, yeah.
- Yeah, I mean I've
got to be a Bellerian,
otherwise I wouldn't
be dressed like this.
Gosh, am I a Bellerian?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I have to be.
Yep, yep, I'm a Bellerian.
Oh hell, am I?
No, no, no, I am a Bellerian.
I am, mm-hmm.
- Guard!
Guard, sick man, we
need more moisturizer!
- Hey, love giver,
I may have a way for
us to get outta here!
- What, how?
- Well it just so happens
that a clever young ape
named Bobo just might be
able to regurgitate up a key
that'll undo these locks!
- Bobo, that's remarkable.
You lifted a key off a guard
and you've smuggled
it in your stomach?
- Well no, actually, the
fact of the matter is
that I've swallowed so darn
many things over the years
there must be a key down
there somewhere that'll work.
(Pearl groaning)
- Do I wanna get
free that badly?
(Bobo groaning)
A comb?
Where'd that come from?
Oh that's right, I swallowed
a bunch of that blue stuff
at the barber's so I got a
couple of those in there.
- Would you just--
- I'm doing it.
(Bobo gagging)
Oh, a Zippo, what do you know?
Wait, wait.
(Bobo gagging)
A hairpin!
- He swallowed a woman,
he swallowed a woman!
- I did not, brain
guy, I swallowed a wig.
Let me just see if I
can undo this lock here.
Yes, yes, I'm free!
- Oh great, Bobo, great, great.
Okay, Bobo, listen
very carefully,
go get Observer's brain
and bring it back here.
We'll be outta here in no time.
- Leave it to Mr. Stealth.
(chuckling)
(door creaking)
Oh!
(laughing)
- I like lettuce.
- Shut up.
- Okay.
- Bobo, where's
Observer's brain?
- Oh please--
- What are you doing?
- Would you just give me
a little bit of credit?
I mean, for crying out loud,
I have screwed up so
many things in the past,
I'd just like an opportunity
to redeem myself.
Oh.
I was supposed to get
Observer's brain wasn't I?
(sighing)
And now you're probably
mad at me, aren't ya?
And I suppose you want me to
hit myself now, don't you?
(groaning)
My hand's up here.
Oh, good angle.
Could I regurgitate up
anything to make it up for you?
- Well I'll take some lettuce
if you have any lettuce.
- Coming up.
- Okay, okay, okay, ask me if
I'm a Bellerian, point blank.
- Are you a Bellarian?
- No!
Damn, I'm not.
What am I then, am I just some
kind of a gauzy fruitcake?
Am I just some kind
of a gullible freak
who allows the core of
his own being to be blown
to the four winds, I mean,
well, I guess so then.
Well, that's what I am
then, a gullible freak.
Good, good.
Wait, wait, what am I again?
(alarm blaring)
- We've got movies inside!
- I'll figure it out later!
(doors opening)
I look good as a Bellarian.
- Oh you do, it's just...
(man groaning)
- [Tom] Ooh.
- [Crow] You know, Mike,
take away all the muscle mass
on this Ryder guy,
it's pretty much you.
- [Mike] Yeah, yeah.
You know, they shouldn't have
set their phasers to miss.
- [Tom] Oh, railing kill.
- [Crow] No really, take
away his personality
and the fact that women are
attracted to him and it's you.
- [Mike] Thank you,
that's fine for me.
(man yelling)
- He killed Mitch Gaylord!
- Flint Ironstag.
- Bolt Vanderhuge.
- [Tom] Whee!
- [Mike] This is exciting as
exciting can be, I must say.
- [Crow] Got panty creep.
(groaning)
- [Mike] Methane?
- [Tom] Oh no, the methane,
how are they gonna
fill their cows?
- [Mike] Thick McRunfast.
(Tom groaning)
- Forget it, they're
heading for the bridge.
- [Tom] My skull's
almost out now.
- Get back to your posts.
Let's go.
- Move!
- [Tom] You stay with me, Trent.
- [Computer] Welcome,
Commander Jansen,
how may I help you?
- Open file on--
- Blitzen.
- Bellarian behavior.
- [Computer] Bellarian behavior,
order of high priestesses.
- Bellarians.
- Mm-hmm.
- [Computer] Non planet-based
practitioners of magic.
- [Crow] See, these
balls, magic huh?
(mysterious music)
- [Tom] Mosquito, got it.
- [Mike] The Stevie
Nicks workout.
- [Jennera] Commander.
- [Tom] Have you
signed Sherry's card?
- [Jennera] It is now
time for us to talk.
- You?
- Yes.
I am Jennera, the
14th High Priestess
of the Tripton lineage.
- Uh huh, right.
- [Jennera] The people
of the Southern Sun
are no longer able to
distinguish light from dark.
Your people are falling prey
to the powers of darkness.
Listen, I speak the truth.
- [Crow] Actually, she
thinks the truth very loudly.
- [Tom] Ho ho, ho?
- [Mike] Finally,
Christmas comes to Santa.
- [Crow] Mrs. Kringle and
I have an understanding.
- [Tom] It's basically
over between us.
- [Mike] Wanna see me shake
like a bowl full of jelly?
- [Crow] Ho ho ho ho ho.
- [Tom] Ho ho, someone did
leave a cookie out for me.
Ho ho ho.
- [Mike] I am a
right jolly old elf.
- What happened?
- [Jennera] I have shared
with you the way to truth.
Now you must use
what you have learned
to face Kalgan and his evil.
- I will.
- [Crow] Let me just
check you twice here.
- My father and his
father before him--
- [Tom] Also taped
wool to their faces.
- Both reasonable men.
I myself have tried to
follow in their footsteps.
I'm a man who believes
in peace, not war.
Captain Devers and I
have decided, David--
- [Tom] You're fired.
- If you will accept, we
would like to name you
as our new Flight Commander.
- I mean, attendant.
- And we trust and pray
you will maintain this
as a ship of peace.
- Rockin'!
- And we will in due course
let all the people know
and warn them of
Kalgan and his men.
- [Tom] Yeah, I
was gonna say that.
- Well, David,
good luck.
- [Mike] We put our faith
in Blast Hardcheese.
- [Crow] I'm gonna go let the
Bellarians play under my robe.
- Whoa.
- Ugh.
- [Tom] Hey, Sherry's
birthday party, finally!
- [Mike] Hey, she's nude!
- [Tom] Fully nude.
- [Crow] Ah,
Lieutenant Waitress.
- [Tom] Yep, yep,
she's a graduate of MIT
but she still has to
serve drinks to men.
- [Mike] Okay,
that's two Bullshots
and a Pink Squirrel here.
- Well, David, cheers.
- Cheers.
- [Crow] Buff Drinklots.
- [Tom] It's real fruit flavor.
- It's a great honor
serving you and your ship,
the Southern Sun.
- Here's to you, David.
- And happiness?
(Commander chuckling)
- That's what it's all about.
- [Mike] Woo hoo, we
got ISO 9001 certified!
- Commander, where's Lea?
- [Crow] Take that back!
- Lea?
Oh, Lea.
- [Tom] My grandma daughter.
- David, I think you'll
find her in her usual place.
- [Mike] Hiding from you.
- The greenhouse.
- 'Scuse me.
- Yes.
- [Crow] He's gonna have so
much sex with your daughter.
- Well, Captain, can
you remember when
you were that young?
- [Tom] I am that young.
- Be damned if I can.
- [Mike] Oh, Slab,
oh Hunk, oh Flink.
- [Crow] Why do you need that
guy over there to spot you?
(Tom groaning)
- [Tom] Thanks, this is
really good for my abs.
- [Crow] She dusted herself
with super weight gain powder
to attract him.
(sentimental music)
- [Mike] No.
Ick, no, wrong.
No, nothing, nothing.
Stop, now what it that?
Cut it out, Clod, no.
Not there, no, look,
just get off me.
- [Crow] Hey, you wanna
wrap it up, Chunky?
There's a tour coming through.
(mysterious music)
- [Mike] Super intelligent
dandelion seeds.
- [Tom] They'll
worship anything.
- [Crow] Okay, practice
your dog paddle, ladies.
(mysterious music)
- [Tom] I can't get
this water outta my ear.
- [Mike] Oh, I hate food.
It's my people.
- [Tom] Can I
borrow a cup of sex?
- [Crow] Man, she
makes Shelley Duvall
look like Shirley Hemphill.
(mysterious music)
- Come on, it'll be all right.
- [Mike] You stupid food lovers.
- [Crow] Bellarians.
Pantene Pro-V
- [Mike] Glenda Jackson is
Kate Moss as Isadora Duncan.
- [Tom] Red Rover, Red
Rover, let Jimmy come over.
(Tom vocalizing)
♪ Oh right ♪
- Why didn't you
call me the second
they deserted their post?
- Wow, man.
- [Man] The minute they
didn't respond, I came to you.
I didn't know what else to do.
- [Man] What happened?
- [Mike] They rocked us
like a hurricane, sir.
- [Man] Talk to me,
what happened, huh?
- Happened?
- Some happened.
- Nothing happened.
- [Crow] We just talked and
looked at glowing balls.
- Kalgan warned us
about these women.
- Knock it off, Colton!
Grab these idiots, take
'em down to refrigeration
and put 'em on ice.
- [Mike] But we're
all idiots, sir.
- [Ranger] Heads are gonna roll
when Kalgan finds
out about this.
- [Tom] But we were just working
on some night moves, sir.
- [Crow] Not a
Bellarian anymore.
- [Mike] Yeah, I see that.
- [Crow] Come on,
Metamucil, work your magic.
(Tom snoring)
- Is this the man?
- [Mike] Why no,
sir, you da man.
- Soften him up.
- [Tom] So Lance
Kerwin is their thug.
- [Crow] What are you doing?
By soften I meant
moisturize him.
- [Mike] He's an
artist with a fist.
- [Tom] Quiet,
Mitch Miller's on!
- [Man] No, no more!
- [Crow] Okay, little more then.
- I don't like people
who make mistakes.
We're going to put you
on ice for a while.
- [Mike] On Vanilla Ice.
- Wait, I wanna know
what's going on.
What's happening with my men?
- Blake.
- What's the matter, ranger?
Afraid you're losing control?
- Yes.
I'm losing control over my men
and over what I'm
responsible for.
- Don't be so naive,
you want off this ship
as much as anybody.
- That may be true
but I'm not willing
to sacrifice the lives of--
- Look.
- It's over, Tad.
- Kalgan's got his plan.
We're getting off this ship
with the help of the pirates
and there's nothing you
nor I nor anybody else
can do about it.
- Bitch.
- [Pirate] This is the
Alseca Pirate Fleet,
to those onboard the Southern
Sun, listen carefully.
- Good mornin'!
- You have entered
the Alpha Delta Restricted Zone,
we have claim on this
section of space.
Surrender immediately
or be blown--
- Yeah.
- Into astro dust.
(lasers firing)
- [Tom] Shot of a
previous explosion!
- [Announcer] Red alert, red
alert, we are under fire!
We are under fire.
- Okay, gotta go, Gary.
- [Computer] Target
space ships in range,
prepare to fire missiles.
- Fire nipples?
- That's what he said.
- [Computer] Fire one.
(space ship exploding)
- [Mike] Death, death, death.
- [Computer] Fire two.
- [Tom] The Honeymooners!
- [Computer] Pirate ship
terminated, return to post.
- [Crow] God, I love Pac-Man!
- [Announcer] To all
onboard, congratulations,
we have successfully defended--
- She's the nude girl again.
- The Southern Sun
against the latest
pirate attack.
- [Mike] They're
having the same party.
- [Announcer] But we must now
focus on internal problems.
- [Tom] The white Commodores!
- May I have your
attention please?
The officers of the watch
please form three groups.
The first group is
gonna be responsible
for making weapons.
- Making woppits?
- [Dave] The second group
is going to act as soldiers!
- [Mike] Sir, we were on break.
- [Dave] The third
group is responsible
for getting food and supplies.
- Arr.
- I suggest we close off
all entries and exits
to the engine room.
We're going to hold out
here and never let 'em
take over the Southern Sun!
Let's get out there
and kick some ass!
(cheering)
- Trunk Slamchest.
- Fist Rockbone.
- Stump Beefknob.
- Smash Lampjaw.
- [Crow] So you usually see
Denise to do your hair, huh?
(suspenseful music)
- [Mike] I'd like some
mixed flowers for my eunuch.
- Lovely spot, isn't it?
- What are you doing here?
- You're much more attractive
with your mouth shut.
Bring her to my
headquarters at once.
- [Tom] And get her some pants.
(Lea groaning)
- [Mike] Oh, she's really
struggling, I must say.
She's going mental on us,
but then again she isn't.
- [Tom] Don't touch my
chin tuck, it's new!
- [Kalgan] Let's go!
(laughing)
- [Crow] Oh, well I thought
it was funny anyway.
(suspenseful music)
- Jason, go get Lea, I want
her on the bridge immediately.
- [Tom] It's Lieutenant
Commander Jason.
- [Mike] Jason.
- Commander, message coming
through on channel 16.
- [Mike] What do ya got
for me, Rick Astley?
- Jansen, I've
something to show you.
- I've got your mother.
- Oh no.
- You have 12 hours to
surrender the bridge,
otherwise your daughter will
be jettisoned into space.
- Well, no downside.
- Well, Captain?
- Kalgan lives like that,
Sir, he lives by the sword.
- [Mike] I thought he
lived by the galley.
(Crow groaning)
- He's evil, ruthless.
There are many people
onboard this ship, Sir.
- [Mike] Oi.
- We have to fight back.
- Strewth.
- Go on.
- Sir, we both know
that there's only
one man on the ship
who's capable of combat.
- Too right.
- Who's had the training,
physically and mentally.
- All right.
- [Crow] Fetch me
my warrior muumuu.
- We will prepare for battle.
- [Tom] The crowd
stands and applauds
as she's helped off the movie.
- [Mike] You animals, how
can I do ab crunches in this?
- Let me introduce you to the
high intensity probing laser.
I do have one weakness, pain.
- And French silk pie.
- Other people's.
Now, I'm going to use this
laser on one of your teeth.
It works not unlike
ancient dental equipment.
Not that you'd know
anything about that.
- [Tom] You're too stupid to
learn about dental history.
- Bastard!
- [Mike] How dare you
insult my knowledge
of ancient dentistry.
- Now, about your father's
contingency plans?
- You bastard!
- Whoa.
- [Crow] Can't believe it,
there's a sale on PowerBars!
Those things never
go on sale, man.
(knocking)
- [Tom] Huh.
Sounds like you're
knocking, Tom,
you might need some premium gas.
- [Mike] They really
need the masks?
- [Crow] Punch Rockgroin.
(men yelling)
- Railing kill!
- Railing kill, all right.
- [Tom] There must be
a very elderly woman
with the flu under that costume.
- Buck Plankchest.
- Stump Chunkman.
- Dirk Hardpeck.
- Rip Steakface.
- Slate Slabrock.
- Crud Bonemeal.
- What a shame to burn
out these lovely teeth.
I want those countermeasures!
- Brick Hardmeat.
(Tom giggling)
- [Crow] So he fits into a
suit that was restrictive
on a really small man?
(beeping)
- [Mike] What was that
sound, was that you, Servo?
- [Tom] No, mine are quiet.
- [Crow] Ah, it's the laser
that whirs like a drill.
- [Mike] Just keep smiling,
don't let him know
it bothers you.
(laser whirring)
- I don't feel a thing.
- [Tom] I'm an
emotionally-stunted man.
(Kalgan laughing)
- [Crow] I had a
prophylaxis scheduled.
- [Mike] Can you sign a check
so I can go to Office Max?
(Ranger coughing)
- Turn it off!
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Does his entrance
warrant a dun dun dun dun?
- [Crow] Nope.
- I see you've got the girl.
- I had to let them
know we meant business.
- Girl?
- I'd better get back
to the engine room
before they miss me.
- Come, I'll take you.
- [Crow] So why did he
wander out of the engine room
in the first place?
Jeez!
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] Damn AOL.
(guard sighing)
- [Crow] Wall-mounted keyboards,
it must be the future!
(beeping)
- [Joseph] Hey Murray,
it's Joseph here.
- Murray.
- Yo, pal!
- Hey listen, my
monitor's gone off again.
- [Murray] I'll schedule
you for next week.
- Well can't you
fix it any sooner?
- [Murray] We're
backed up already!
- Okay, whenever you can.
- Anything for you, buddy.
- Okay, take it easy.
- [Tom] The computer
problems of Murray and Joe
make for gripping cinema.
I saw a ghost!
- Whip Slagcheek.
- Punch Sideiron.
- [Mike] Gristle McThornbody.
- Hey you.
Come here.
- [Crow] Do you mean me
or my familiar over there?
- Yeah, you, come here.
- [Tom] Yes, a man born
without a brain stem.
- Closer.
- [Mike] You know, the last
eight times this happened
the woman just
wanted to get away.
- Closer.
- [Crow] You had a little
popcorn on your lip,
it was bothering me.
- Closer.
Oh yeah.
- [Tom] This is just like the
time I got lost at Bally's.
Wandered onto the tennis
courts, couldn't get out.
- [Mike] Standing right
under a toilet outlet there.
- Slake Fistcrunch.
- Buff Hardback.
- [Tom] Bob Johnson, no, wait.
(Dave gasping)
- [Mike] You're
lucky the smart guard
is on vacation this week.
- [Tom] Morgan Fairchild
and Phil Collins, no!
- Ooh!
- [Crow] I see a sunken chest!
- [Mike] Oh, please, my
breasts are very sensitive.
- Oh yeah.
- Is the rest of the
equipment as good as that?
- [Guard] Let's have a look.
- What's he doing, Mike?
- Yeah.
- I don't think you guys--
- I'll make you a trade.
First your trousers.
- Just this part.
- And then you can
see everything.
- [Crow] This is supposed
to be an ipecac, right?
- Okay.
(suspenseful music)
- [Mike] That's the cast
of The Poseidon Adventure
coming the other way.
- [Tom] Oh jeez, the
guy's just coming down
to scoop out the cat box.
- [Mike] Look, I'm
sorry whoever you are,
I was just getting
really frustrated.
- No!
- No, no!
(stammering)
- I don't.
- Okay!
- It's all I got.
- My shoe.
- Shoe, shoe!
(all groaning)
- [Tom] Yuck.
(guard yelling)
- [Mike] Holy cow, that was
totally outta left field.
- Blast Thickneck.
- Crunch Buttsteak.
- [Mike] Slam Squattrust.
- [Tom] Oh, you lovable trollop.
- What took ya so long?
- I've been busy too.
Let's get his clothes.
- [Crow] Oh, so it's
gonna be a three way.
Okay, that's fine, guys.
(door swishing)
- Rawhide.
Rawhide.
(guard yelling)
- Let's go.
- [Tom] Come on,
I found this place
that makes these
really healthy shakes.
- Come on, move,
move, move, move!
Come on, move!
- I'm moving, bossy boots!
- [Mike] Come on, move, move,
move, you see how it feels?
Move!
- [Tom] Lump Beefbroth.
- [Crow] Move, move,
move, move, move!
- No, you move!
- No, you move, move!
- [Mike] No, you move!
- [Tom] Okay, now
move, move one leg
then move the other,
now breathe, breathe.
Now make your heart
beat, come on!
(suspenseful music)
- [Crow] You can see
right up their jumpsuits.
- [Mike] Did you sign Sherry's
belated birthday card?
- [Tom] Move, move, no, don't.
(man yelling)
- [Mike] How y'all doin'?
- [Crow] Ow, my mask!
- Here, put this on, okay?
- [Tom] But I just
loosed my hair.
- [Mike] These will make it
so we can't see anything.
- All right, let's move.
(muffled yelling)
- [Mike] The boiler
room has a receptionist?
- [Dave] All right, let's go.
- [Tom] And have
concluded that the boilers
have not moved for some time.
(computer beeping)
- [Guard] Hey, you
guys, let's see some ID.
- [Crow] Not technically a
railing but the same spirit.
- [Mike] Sure, sure.
(man groaning)
Ow, why do you hate
my groin so much?
- [Crow] I don't, Mike.
- Not you, Crow.
- All right, let's move.
- [Tom] I mean,
move, move, move!
- [Crow] Stupid freshmen!
- Have you located the girl?
- [Tom] I'll poke
my skull out at you!
- Answer me!
(growling)
I'm surrounded by incompetence!
I'm being undermined
by my own disciples!
You let that space bitch
slip through our fingers!
She was our--
- What do you call that?
- Where's that idiot
who let her escape?
- We've got him on ice, sir.
- Kill him at once!
- Yes sir.
- And then tell MacPhearson
our plan is operational.
Put the entire
squad on red alert!
(alarm blaring)
- [Crow] They woke up
the Oak Ridge Boys!
♪ Elvira ♪
(doors closing)
- Oh, say, that's a nice one.
Wrought iron.
- Hey Servo.
(yelling)
- Careful there, Mike.
- Another one of those things.
Servo, do you know
anything about this?
- Oh yeah, I just
installed a bunch
of new safety
railings on the ship.
- Oh really?
(laughing)
Why?
- Why?
What happens when OSHA stops by
and sees everything
completely unrailing, huh?
Big, fat fines, that's what!
But more importantly, Mike,
we've got to want to
do it for ourselves.
- But you can't just put
railings up randomly, I mean--
- You can't?
- There was a railing
in front of the door to my room.
There was an ankle-high
railing around the rugs.
And there was a railing around
the leftover hashbrowns.
I mean, ow!
- I better put a railing
around that railing there.
(Crow yelling)
Ah, Crow just found the
whisper-quiet high-speed
spinning spike railing.
- [Crow] Yeah, cool.
Ow.
- All right, Servo, you've
got one hour to get rid of
every railing on the ship, okay?
One hour, I mean it, all right?
- For crying out loud.
(Mike yelling)
Oh yeah, Mike, I
forgot to tell ya
that I had some moats put
in because it's pretty hard
to justify having
this many railings
without at least having some
big heights to have railings
in front of, know what I mean?
(water splashing)
- Servo!
- We'll be right back.
Hello!
(upbeat music)
- [Mike] Servo, there's
a railing around my seat.
- [Tom] You're welcome.
- Oh, thank God.
- [Mike] I'm okay too.
- [Crow] Hey, how 'bout
some sugar for Sting
and Dolph, here?
- Commander, we have a problem.
- I'm out of Mega Fuel.
- Yes, David?
- MacPhearson's a traitor.
- No.
- Yes, I saw him with Kalgan
at the Enforcer's headquarters.
- I can't believe it,
I mean it could be--
- Dad!
I saw him there today.
- Today?
- That being the
case, this is serious,
he knows our codes,
he has our weapons.
- Weapons?
- He knows all our
countermeasures.
- I find this unbelievable.
- [Tom] Wake up, Gramps.
- He's one of my best men,
he's my Chief Engineer.
- Commander, if I may say so--
- [Crow] You need
to cut some weight.
- Let me do my job.
- I'm coming with you.
- I'm coming too.
- I'm not.
- Captain, I'd
rather do it alone.
- As you please, Dave.
- But thank you.
- [Tom] You're welcome.
- Lea, you stay here.
Commander.
- [Mike] There goes a
big, brave brick of meat.
- [Crow] New, squid in a globe!
(mysterious music)
- [Tom] This is really hard
music to dance to, Cindy.
- [Mike] Laraine Newman
and the Newmanettes!
- [Jennera] One cannot
escape one's own destiny.
- [Crow] But one can delay it
indefinitely and have a beer.
(alarm blaring)
- We're going in!
- [Tom] I clogged up the
toilet but we're going in!
- [Mike] Aw, now they
stole the Enterprise's
red alert sound thingy.
- [Crow] Well, 86 the
pan-seared tuna, you guys,
chef says we're all out.
- [Tom] I'm gonna miss
this old wherever we are.
- [Mike] Don't get
smart with me, ceiling.
- Touch Rustrod.
- Reef Blastbody.
(suspenseful music)
- [Tom] Coach has us
doing wind sprints.
(vocalizing)
- [Tom] Sounds like Kitaro
fell asleep on his keyboard.
(vocalizing)
- [Mike] Big McLargeHuge.
- Damn you!
- [Crow] So where the
hell are these two
in relationship to each other?
- Sneaky little.
- Stop right there!
- [Tom] Would you like
to sample some Canoe?
- [Man] We're being
attacked from above,
Commander Ryder, we're
being attacked from above,
the Enforcers are--
(laser firing)
- [Crow] Hold on, let me
come down and tell you.
(man yelling)
Be right there.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Ow, jeez,
cut it out, you guys!
(lasers firing)
- [Crow] Here's little free
advice for the mutineers,
just stop and aim, you idiots!
- [Tom] Why is he so
impossible to hit?
Why do they keep on missing
the slow, giant white thing?
- He's going below!
- After him, move!
- Cut him off, hustle!
- [Mike] Loading up some
railing fodder here.
- [Crow] My flamethrower's
kinda weak here...
(vocalizing)
- Let's go, let's go!
- You know, in this movie
people don't seem to trust
other people's ability
to move forward.
- Yeah.
- [Crow] A horse, my
kingdom for a horse.
(lasers firing)
(vocalizing)
(man yelling)
- [Tom] Ooh, someone
get me a Zantac, quick!
- 300s.
(vocalizing)
- [Mike] Oh, send
my mask to Mother.
- [Crow] Stay together
cheeks, stay together cheeks.
- [Tom] Well, they rented
a pneumatic catapult
and damn it, they're
gonna use it.
- So many good lives wasted.
- Not these guy's lives.
- War always brings
out the worst in man.
I don't know.
I feel that I failed.
- You did, Daddy!
- Don't blame yourself,
it had to happen.
There was no compromise.
- [Tom] That scene really
makes me stop and think
about how much better a root
canal would be than this movie!
- [Mike] I think
they just borrowed
the South High
marching band uniforms.
- [Crow] So this takes place
at the Anheuser Busch brewery
or...
- [Mike] Oh, they're
having a craft fair.
(suspenseful music)
- [Tom] Giant toilet
seat hanging there.
- [Crow] Yeah, handicapped
accessible, I don't think so.
(laser firing)
- [Mike] Please don't
use those stairs.
(men yelling)
- [Crow] Please
don't shoot us, okay,
but you don't get
a boxed lunch then.
- [Mike] You know, it
has to be noted that
Captain Santa Claus
really is failing here.
- [Crow] Absolutely.
- [Tom] See, I'm handicapable.
- [Crow] The railing
contributed to his death, there,
that's a railing death.
- [Mike] Smoke Manmuscle.
- [Tom] See, if I
hadn't lifted so much
those rays would hurt me.
- [Crow] Oh, he
needs a giant Tucks.
- Out of my way, you idiot!
- [Mike] Stupid Buddhist monk,
the Vietnam War's been over
for hundreds of years!
- [Tom] If there's one
thing this movie does well
it's tossing Canadians around.
- Canadians?
- Oh come on, Mike,
this movie's ripe with
the stench of back bacon.
- [Mike] If you say so.
- [Crow] Wow, I am on
the edge of my seat!
I should probably
scoot back a little,
be more comfortable.
- Yeah, you got a lot
more room there.
- Rest of the movie.
(murmuring)
- [Tom] I still support
the railing system!
- [Mike] Hey, Don,
can I work in here?
(lasers firing)
(men yelling)
- Wahoo, whee!
- All you guys get back
to the engine room!
Go!
(Crow yelling)
- [Mike] I'll loosen up the
paint, we can scrape later!
(lasers firing)
- Let's get outta here!
Back to the engine room!
Move, move!
- [Crow] Does he suddenly have
golf-ball-sized throat nodes?
- [Mike] Oh, watch the
groin, ow, watch the groin.
- [Crow] Seems to me that
randomly blowing up things
is not a good strategy
in a space ship.
(hooting)
- Fire!
- Don't waste your time,
you'll never get through there!
- [Crow] I must say.
- You'll get singed, it's over!
Let's get out of here.
- [Mike] We're being totally
defeated, I must say.
- [Tom] Eat Punchbeef.
- I'm leaving.
- Lea.
- [Mike] You wanna
get me some coffee?
- Lea.
- Get me some coffee!
- Lea, come back!
- Forget it, Devey.
- My name's not Debbie!
- You can't stop love.
- [Crow] He must've
blown out his knee
in an earlier mutiny.
(MacPhearson gasping)
- Oh, this is new!
- It says in the Bellerian
book the universal truth
will always prevail.
MacPhearson, your time has come.
You are the first.
- [Tom] I wonder if it's
too late to un-mutiny.
- [Crow] Now that
is exciting, Mike!
That guy just fell over
a railing as he died.
Now tell me that
isn't a good movie
after seeing something like--
- Take it easy.
- [Crow] Feel good.
- [Mike] Hack Blowfist.
- [Crow] Ow, watch it, man!
(Dave yelling)
- Is he all right?
(Tom yelling)
- Lea!
MacPhearson!
- [Mike] That's a really
good strut suspension!
- [Crow] Spider
Skank, Spider Skank.
(Lea screaming)
- Who took my purse?
(screaming)
- [Crow] Oh man, I
shouldn't have ridden
my recumbent bike to work.
- [Tom] Ah, into
a nice sitz bath.
Ah!
- He's gone into the
gas expulsion sump.
- Ryder!
It doesn't have to be this way!
- [Crow] I love you!
- Think about it, we
can work this thing out!
- [Tom] We'll get
couple's counseling!
- [MacPhearson] I didn't have
anything to do with this!
- [Mike] Sorry,
loose valve here.
What were you saying?
- What are you doing, man?
- What's that smell,
what are you doing?
- [Crow] Man,
Chunkhead just beefed.
- [Tom] I got the gas grill
going, you guys want burgers?
(fire crackling)
- No!
- [Mike] And our brave hero
roasts the disabled man.
- [Crow] Well, I have learned
one thing from this movie,
Mike, not to sit in
our gas expulsion sump.
We've gotta stop
having lunch there.
- [Mike] That's a good point.
(upbeat music)
- You should've stayed
up on the bridge
safe with your father!
- Hey guys.
- The Enforcers are not
going to attack again.
- [Mike] Let's see
just how big this is.
- Well if you'd shut up--
- Oh yeah.
- Wow.
- That's impressive.
- Kalgan's dead.
- Pretty beefy.
- Quiet.
- They have no leader,
they have no choice but
to surrender to my father.
- [Mike] Hey guys, just
dropped the reports off.
- Besides, I thought
you'd be happy to see me.
- 'Course I am.
But that's not the issue, your
father should've stopped you.
- My father stopped
interfering with my life
when I was 15 years old.
- [Mike] Hey again, guys,
just forgot something.
- He's a good man, I just
wish he could control you
as well as he does this ship.
- [Crow] You mean
have a mutiny on me?
- [Lea] Control me?
If I hadn't saved you
in that engine room--
- Oh come on, I would've
got out of that situation,
no problem.
(Tom laughing)
- Well that's gratitude.
- Gratitude?
Stop throwing your
$10 words around!
- Why did you do it?
- Because...
Oh, never mind.
You really are stubborn.
- Does that mean I'm cut?
(suspenseful music)
♪ Music that means,
means, means ♪
♪ Nothing at all, all, all ♪
(vocalizing)
- [Jannera] Now it
is time for Kalgan.
- [Tom] Recommended
by top breeders.
- [Mike] He's gearing up for
a really intense video game.
- [Crow] Oh man, why is
this seat so far forward?
Who was driving this thing last?
(vocalizing)
- [Mike] Well, someone
dropped a jar of Hellmanns
in aisle seven, I
gotta go clean it up.
(vocalizing)
- [Tom] Evil evil, put
put put put, evil evil.
(dramatic music)
Push on, mighty Cushman!
- [Crow] These
things are a riot!
- [Tom] Oh, didn't see ya,
my fault, totally my fault.
- Lea, you all right?
- Fine.
- [Dave] Son of a...
(vocalizing)
- [Crow] Damn, I'm losing
speed 'cause I'm also trying
to buff the floors!
(vocalizing)
- [Mike] Sorry, you cut
me off by the boiler,
it just ticked me off.
- [Tom] You know, in
their silliest moments,
the Three Stooges never reached
this level of indignity.
- [Mike] You know, a lot of
people have compared this scene
to the climactic chariot
scene in Ben-Hur?
- Uh-huh?
- Yeah, you know,
they usually say,
"Ben-Hur was really good,
"this movie totally sucks."
- That follows.
- You'll wish you'd
never come here, Ryder!
- [Crow] Lea help,
Kalgan's chasing me!
- [Tom] Active Senior's
Lifestyle says,
"Thumb's up, it will
make your heart race,
"though maybe that's
not such a good thing."
- [Crow] Any second, Lea's
gonna jump on her Big Wheel
and give chase.
- I'm gonna get
you, you bastard!
- Meddling fool!
(Mike laughing)
- [Mike] What, is
he Snidely Whiplash?
- [Tom] You know,
you can actually get
another three miles an
hour in these babies
if you take it off
the shag setting.
(lasers firing)
- [Crow] Accursed mountebank!
- Lea, get out of the way!
- [Mike] Do you think he
used a wire bottle brush
inside his throat before
he filmed this scene?
- [Tom] Toro, Toro, these
things are made by Toro!
- [Crow] Still, it's better
than Days of Thunder.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Lea, look out!
- Oh, this is a riot!
- Go!
- Take this, you space bitch!
- [Tom] That's for
not knowing anything
about ancient dentistry!
(laughing)
- Come on!
- Son of a,
oh I forgot to step on the gas.
(laughing)
- Oh, well, anyway.
- Bastard.
(yelling)
- [Crow] Well, anyway,
got that out of my system.
- [Mike] Roll Fizzlebeef.
- No!
(Tom laughing)
- [Tom] Oh boy.
- [Mike] Wow, big explosion
for a tiny electric cart.
- [Crow] Yeah, he shouldn't
have been carrying
that case of cleaning
fluid and nitroglycerin
and gelignite in there.
- [Tom] Plus he microwaved
an egg at the same time.
- [Mike] Finally got
some time to lift.
- Lea, Lea, you okay?
- [Crow] Come on,
move, move, move, move!
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
What happened?
- Okay.
- Don't worry about it,
Kalgan's gone forever.
- [Mike] I'm guessing.
- He's finished.
(Tom laughing)
- Oh boy.
- Thank god.
- Yeah.
- [Crow] Thank my
personal trainer.
- Let's get outta here.
- [Mike] Come on,
move, move, move, move!
- [Tom] Not since the Fuzzy
Zoeller, Lee Trevino collision
of 1974 has there been such a
horrible golf cart accident.
- [Mike] Kinda wish we had
some marshmallows, you know?
We could stuff 'em
in our eyes and ears
and never have to see or
hear this stupid movie!
- [Crow] Lea, this could
be the start of a beautiful
alternate-day bulk-up routine.
- [Announcer] Attention,
Commander Ryder,
Stingray Patrol
ready for takeoff.
- Won't you miss your flight?
- Does that mean
you won't marry me?
- [Tom] Huh?
- Oh Dave.
- [Crow] I think you
skipped a line, honey.
- [Mike] There we go,
I got a little bit
of a workout in at last.
- [Crow] Hey, there's a
little draft over there,
let's make out over here.
- [Tom] They married
and had a healthy
eight and a half
pound pork roast.
- [Mike] Oh, I think Chunkhead's
more of a shuttle craft
if you know what I'm saying?
- Yes, sir.
(Tom laughing)
- [Tom] Good, good, back to
the rusting septic system
of this futuristic space ship!
(suspenseful music)
- [Mike] I hope they
spend the last few minutes
on the apology.
- [Tom] I heard there's
a tacked-on bit of film
featuring the Attorney
General explaining
how you can join in
a class-action suit
against this movie.
There is.
- Well.
- Right.
Okay, pans over and
Kalgan wakes up.
- [Tom] Yeah, yeah,
and there's Kalgan--
- [Crow] Yeah, yeah,
we're all really surprised
'cause wow, we already
saw Kalgan die.
(crosstalk)
- Flaming hand sticking out.
- [Crow] Can we just move
it along now, people?
- [Mike] What, is he
waiting for his pants
to come out of the dryer?
- [Tom] I don't know.
(Crow laughing)
- Oh, ow, I'm too sore.
- [Mike] Cajun
pan-blackened Kalgan.
- And his eyes open,
and his eyes open.
- And his eyes open.
- Eyes open.
- His eyes open.
- Come on!
- [Tom] I'm sitting
in something wet.
- [Crow] Me, take me away.
- [Mike] We don't
need more Calgon.
(suspenseful music)
- Boo, boo!
- Boy, you know,
a retarded jellyfish could
make a better movie than this.
- [Crow] A
severely-impaired box turtle
with a very busy schedule, just
give him a camera for a day,
he'd come up with
something better than this.
- [Mike] Music rejected
by the band Survivor.
♪ Said I'm a fool ♪
- Uh-huh?
♪ Because I believe ♪
- Hold on here.
♪ I know enough ♪
- He knows enough!
♪ To know I can dream ♪
- Me too,
I feel like that sometimes too!
♪ Nowhere ♪
- Yeah.
- [Crow] The lobster man
was played by Guy Pringle.
- [Mike] Oh, wouldn't wanna
slam a stack of that guy.
♪ My moment is now ♪
♪ She's a maniac,
maniac on the floor ♪
♪ Don't pay the ferryman ♪
♪ Don't even fix that price ♪
♪ Here I am, maniac,
maniac on the floor ♪
- [Tom] Everybody.
♪ Someday, love will find you ♪
- [Mike] Hey, the
Bellerians, all right!
- [Crow] Hi, my name is Jeanet
Moltke, I'm a Bellerian,
this is my friend Laure
Fremont, she's a Bellerian too.
♪ There's no feeling ♪
♪ I'm eager to ♪
- You know,
it is statistically proven
that 78% of white guys
can sing like this.
- Really?
- [Mike] So no one
else wants to cry.
♪ Maybe I'll fly ♪
- Though I highly doubt it!
♪ Here I stand ♪
- [Crow] I'm staying
in my parent's basement
'til I find a job!
- [Tom] Continuity,
Bev Wilbraham,
can she be legally arrested now?
- [Mike] You know,
they really did have
excellent clapping and loading.
- [Crow] So the best boy
that they could come up with
was Fuzzy Skinner?
(Tom laughing)
♪ Edge of a dream ♪
- [Mike] Hey, hold
on, I got one.
♪ I wear my sunglasses
at night so I can't ♪
- Appropriate.
- Uh-huh.
- [Crow] This band will
be appearing at the Bombay
Bicycle Club later this weekend!
- [Tom] Okay, okay
Mike, be honest with us.
This music kinda really
gets your blood going, huh?
- [Crow] Yeah, Mike,
this is your music,
done by your people so I blame
you for this entire movie.
- [Tom] It's just like you
to make a movie like this.
Jeez, Mike.
- Hey, I hated it too,
what are you picking on me for?
- [Crow] Well you
were a young guy
during the 80s weren't you?
I mean, this is your
world, admit it.
- [Tom] Come on, come on.
- [Crow] Okay, now this,
this here's the kinda music
you get all weepy-eyed
at the end of a
drunken Friday night,
sitting there with your
hair all feathered,
scarfing down cold potato skins.
- [Tom] Your attempt to get
little Susie what's-her-name
drunk on lime vodka ended
in humiliating rejection.
- Right.
- So you sit there,
all mushy and sentimental,
reciting to yourself
the words to some song by
Night Ranger, you're pathetic.
- [Crow] Maybe one homely
girl feels sorry for you
for a second but then she sees
how stinkin' drunk you are
and gets disgusted.
- [Tom] And maybe the first
the first-chair trombone player
from the high school
band comes by, you know?
And he takes pity on you, tries
to drive you home and all.
Oh, but no, Mike--
- No!
- [Tom] You wanna swerve home
in your cherried-out
Dodge Charger.
- [Crow] Yeah, you wind
up wrestling for your keys
with the guy and then finally
he drops you with one punch
and he leaves and
you lie there knowing
you got your butt
kicked by the leader
of the high school band.
- You're pathetic.
- You and your 80s.
- Your precious 80s.
- [Crow] You know, it would've
continued to be the 70s
if not for you!
- Yeah!
- [Mike] All right, all right,
that's it, that tears it!
- [Tom] Hey come here, you!
- [Mike] You want a piece of me?
- It's go time, 80s man!
- Come on!
Come on, come on, come on!
- [Crow] I'll take you,
I'll take you, 80s jerk!
- [Tom] Come on, cool breeze!
- [Mike] Owie, ow, don't!
Wait, you guys, wait,
this is nuts, man.
- [Tom] Yes it is, you
hair-feathering freak!
Get him!
- No, Servo, he's right,
he's right, this movie has
us turning on each other.
It won't end, these
credits just won't end!
- [Tom] It's just
like the stupid 80s,
they never ended either!
- No, no,
actually they did, Tom,
there there, that's okay.
See, see, there's the
copyright, that means it's over.
- I'm sorry, Mike.
- It's all over, you guys.
I'm sorry too.
(doors closing)
- So what do you think,
am I buff or what?
Am I blue-twisted
cold-rolled steel or what?
- You sure you've
lifted already?
You're not planning to
lift at some future date
or anything?
No, I see it, I see
it, your arm goes along
and then there's a
little bump there.
- There's this little ripped
bicep is what you mean.
Poindexter Crow, you're gone!
No more the pathetic weenie
to be pushed around at will.
- Yeah, great, hey Cambot,
why don't you zoom in
with a macro lens, maybe
we can get a shot of that--
- You don't need no
macro lens, Nelson!
I am superbly buff
and that's that.
- Okay.
- Hey, Mike, can I get
a spot over here, man?
- Servo, you're--
- Yeah, I know,
I've got ape arms
and a colossal tuckus
and all this from one leg press.
I am quite susceptible
to bulking up.
- Well maybe you've done
enough for one day then
there, buddy.
- Probably,
but I'm addicted now,
if I don't lift I die
so if I could get
a spot over here.
- Yeah sure, no problem, man,
first I gotta talk to
Pearl though, all right?
- See, I was going for tone.
(Tom yelling)
- Well, Mike, here I am,
chained to a wall with an
exceptionally stupid monkey.
- Oh, thank you.
- And a brainless,
drooling nitwit.
- String tastes funny.
- Pearl Forrester,
great life, Pearl.
Good job.
- Oh Pearlie girly, I
thought I'd come down
and remind you that you
die at dawn tomorrow.
You die at dawn tomorrow.
- Your breath stinks.
- Really?
Well, I'll be back
later to remind you.
Bye bye.
- Well, there it is, Mike.
I see no way out.
Observer is useless
without his brain.
- What about my brain?
- So we die tomorrow.
(Bobo groaning)
I guess you guys are free to go.
- All right!
- Woo hoo!
- Shh.
- What?
- Wow,
boy, we're happy and
all that we can go
but we'd really rather
it didn't end this way.
I mean, with you dying
and all, right guys?
- Oh, oh right.
- Yeah, yeah,
this is awkward anyway.
- Yeah!
- Yes!
- Well thank you, but
maybe it's all for the best.
This gives me a chance
to make my peace with
god or whatever.
As I look back on my life, I see
that I've been tormenting
you for no good reason.
And perhaps even
at this late date,
whatever power is over us all
might see fit to forgive me
for all the--
- Is this yours?
Found it over there.
- Hah, my brain!
- Nevermind, Nelson!
Hey, hey, brain guy.
- Yes?
- We need some sort
of distraction for
when Flavia returns.
I know, could you try like
a fake seduction on her?
- Oh, no, no, no, I could
never seduce a woman, Pearl.
- Oh, because you're--
- Oh, I thought you knew,
I am completely and utterly
without a body, I have no body.
- Well thank you for coming
out with that information.
- Oh, I know, let's
get Mike down here!
- Yes, Mike!
- Okay, here we go.
- Very good.
- Oh, Mike!
We need you to try like a
fake seduction on Flavia.
- Oh, well, okay, seducing
a beautiful woman,
not my forte, could maybe give
you 15 to 20 seconds, tops.
- That should be
fine, that's fine.
- If she was old or
lonely or infirm or blind
or something like that--
- Oh, would you please--
- Here she comes!
- I got it, I'm on it,
I'm on it, don't worry about it.
- You, what are you doing here?
- Well hey, if it isn't
Flavia's daughter.
- What does that even mean?
- Well...
- Yeah?
- I guess it just means...
(stammering)
- Yeah?
What, what, come on, what?
- Hah, bingo!
- What in the?
Guards, seize them!
(yelling)
(mouse squeaking)
- Thought I'd just grab
this wheel of Fontina.
(glass shattering)
Oh jeez!
(fire crackling)
(somber music)
(Dave yelling)